this video is about how to see mechanism
这个视频是关于如何看机制的
design as an optimization problem in
设计中的优化问题
particular we can understand the task of
特别是我们可以理解的任务
doing mechanism design as an
做机构设计
optimization that asks us let me find
要求我们的优化让我找到
the best mechanism according to some
根据一些人的最佳机制
kind of definition of best that I'm
我对最佳的定义
interested in given various constraints
对给定的各种限制感兴趣
about how the mechanism has to behave
关于该机制的行为方式
and what kinds of things it's allowed to
以及允许什么样的事情
do so
这样做
in this lecture what I'm going to tell
在这堂课中我要讲的是
you about is some some of the common
你大概是一些共同点
constraints that we impose on mechanism
我们施加在机制上的约束
design and some of the different notions
设计和一些不同的概念
of best that we try to optimize under
我们尝试在以下方面进行优化的最佳方法
these constraints let me begin with
这些限制让我开始
something that we've already spoken
我们已经说过的话
about a bit truthfulness
有点真实
but now I'll define it in the context of
但现在我将在
transferable utility mechanisms so a
可转移的效用机制
transferable utility mechanism is said
据说可转让的效用机制
to be truthful if it is a direct
如果是直接的话要诚实
mechanism and also if it's the case that
机制，如果是这样的话
for all agents and for all valuations
所有代理商和所有估值
that each agent might have an agent eyes
每个特工可能都有特工的眼睛
equilibrium strategy is to disclose
平衡策略是要披露
truthfully so to make his disclosure
如此真实地进行披露
equal to his actual value next I'll say
接下来我要说等于他的实际价值
that a mechanism is strictly Pareto
严格来说是一种机制
efficient or for short just efficient if
高效或简而言之就是高效
in equilibrium it selects a choice X
在平衡中，它选择一个选择X
with the following properties for all
具有以下所有属性
joint valuation vectors that the agents
代理商的联合估值向量
might have and notice that I'm not
可能会注意到我不是
writing a V hat here so I'm saying the
在这里写一个V帽，所以我说
actual evaluations the agents have for
代理商的实际评估
all actual evaluations and for all other
所有实际评估以及所有其他评估
choices that I might make X prime it's
我可能会选择X作素的选择
the case that the sum of the agents
代理人总和的情况
valuations for X is at least as big as
X的估值至少与
the sum of the other agents valuations
其他代理商估值之和
for X prime so in other words a
对于X素数，换句话说a
mechanism is efficient if it selects the
如果选择
choice that maximizes the sums of the
选择最大化的总和
agents actual valuations or their actual
代理商的实际估值或其实际值
utility is disregarding the payments
公用事业无视付款
they'll have to make now you might
他们必须现在就做
notice that in game theory
注意博弈论中
a notion of purrito efficiency which
纯粹效率的概念
seems to be different than this it
似乎与此不同
doesn't talk about summing up valuations
不谈论总结估值
instead it says something about not
相反，它说了一些关于
being purrito dominated by any other
被其他人支配的嘌呤
cell in the game matrix and that seems
游戏矩阵中的单元格，这似乎
pretty different
完全不同
typically when one defines the the game
通常在定义游戏时
theoretic notion of freedom efficiency
自由效率的理论概念
we make a big deal of the fact that
我们做了很多事实，
we're not just talking about summing up
我们不只是在谈论总结
utilities we're talking about the fact
我们正在谈论的实用程序
that utilities are incomparable here it
实用程序在这里无与伦比
sounds like I'm saying free to
听起来我在说...
efficiency allows me just to sum things
效率让我可以总结一下
up so so how is it that I'm getting away
所以我要怎么走
with that well the answer is that if we
有了答案，答案就是，如果我们
think about including the mechanism as
考虑将机制包括在内
an agent if we kind of include them the
一个代理商，如果我们将它们包括在内
person who's actually making these
实际制作这些的人
payments as one of the agents when I
我作为代理人之一付款时
think about efficiency then the payments
考虑效率然后付款
kind of don't matter because they always
没关系，因为他们总是
sum up to zero across all of the agents
所有座席的总和为零
so so basically what's really going to
所以基本上什么是真正的
matter is the choices that get made in
重要的是做出的选择
terms of the the aggregate utility if
聚合效用的条件，如果
I'm ever picking some outcome that is
我从中挑选出一些结果
doesn't maximize the sum of the agents
没有最大化代理商的总和
utilities it's always possible to find a
实用程序，总是可以找到一个
different outcome in which the agents
代理商的不同结果
utilities are maximized so there's more
实用程序已最大化，因此还有更多
utility to go around and then I kind of
实用程序，然后我有点
shuffle the payments around in such a
在这种情况下将付款拖延
way that everybody is at least as happy
每个人至少都快乐的方式
in that situation and the reason
在那种情况下以及原因
intuitively that's possible to do is
凭直觉，这可能是
that there's more money on the table and
桌上还有更多的钱，
so it's it's possible to shuffle things
所以有可能洗牌
instead it's such a way that everybody
而是这样一种方式，每个人
is happier in that circumstance if all
在这种情况下，如果一切都更快乐
that didn't make sense to you then don't
那对你没有意义，那就不要
worry about it what you really need to
担心它您真正需要的是什么
know for the purposes of mechanism
为了机制的目的而知道
design is that it really does make sense
设计是真的有道理
to think of pre to efficiency as
把提高效率视为
maximizing the sum of everyone's values
最大化每个人的价值总和
not their payments just their values let
不是他们的付款，而是他们的价值让
me also note we call this efficiency but
我还注意到我们称这种效率为
there are various other notions of
还有其他各种观念
efficiency that we might care about we
我们可能关心的效率
might care about something like
可能在乎像
computational efficiency how long the
计算效率多长时间
mechanism actually takes to run in cases
该机制实际上需要在某些情况下运行
like that we call this notion of strict
这样我们称之为严格的概念
fritto efficiency economic efficiency to
效率
distinguish it from those other notions
与其他概念区分开来
we also call it social welfare
我们也称其为社会福利
maximization for the obvious reason that
由于明显的原因而最大化
we're we're caring about picking the
我们正在关心挑选
outcome that really does maximize the
确实确实使
sum of the agents utilities and I've
代理商实用程序的总和，我已经
said this before but just to draw your
说过这个，但只是为了画你的
attention to it one last time notice
最后一次注意它
that here I'm talking about the agents
我在这里谈论代理商
actual valuations
实际估值
here's another constraint that we might
这是我们可能遇到的另一个限制
care about budget balance I'll say that
在乎预算平衡，我会说
a transferable utility mechanism is
一种可转移的效用机制是
budget balanced when it's the case that
在这种情况下，预算平衡
for all joint valuations that the agents
对于代理商的所有联合估价
might have and where s is the
可能有，其中s是
equilibrium strategy profile that they
他们的均衡策略简介
follow their equilibrium strategies
遵循他们的均衡策略
given their valuations yield payments
考虑到他们的估值收益支付
that sum to zero so in other words what
总和为零，换句话说，
I'm saying here is that regardless of
我的意思是，无论
what the agents types are in equilibrium
什么是代理类型处于平衡状态
the mechanism both collects and
该机制既收集又
disperses the same amount of money from
从中分散等量的钱
the agents so the mechanism neither
代理商，所以机制既没有
makes nor loses any money as long as the
只要不赚钱也不会亏钱
agents follow their equilibrium
特工遵循他们的平衡
strategies now you might you might
现在的策略，您可能会
wonder why would I want the mechanism
想知道我为什么要这种机制
not to make any money
不赚钱
the answer is it might be that I really
答案可能是我真的
want the money only to serve to get
想要钱只是用来得到
around impossibility theorems and I
围绕不可能定理，我
really just want the mechanism to make
真的只是想让机制
good decisions on the other hand I might
另一方面，我可能会做出好的决定
be running a mechanism and be perfectly
运行机制，做到完美
happy to make money but just be
乐于赚钱，但是只是
concerned about ever losing money in
担心在
that case I would want a relaxed version
那样的话我想要一个轻松的版本
of this condition called weak budget
这种情况称为预算不足
balance and really the only difference
平衡，实际上是唯一的区别
here is I take this equality and I
这是我接受这种平等，我
replace it with an inequality that says
用不等式代替它
I want to make sure that in equilibrium
我想确保平衡
it's never the case that I lose any
从来没有我输过任何东西
money but I'm quite happy to make a
钱，但我很高兴赚到
profit and I can also make other kinds
利润，我也可以做其他的
of variations so just to show you
只是为了向您展示
another one
另一个
it might be too strong to say that no
可能很难说不
matter what the types of the agents are
代理的类型是什么
I never lose any money or I never I
我永远不会亏钱，或者我永远不会
never lose or gain any money I might
永远不要失去或获得任何金钱
prefer to talk ex-ante across the agency
宁愿在整个机构事前交谈
till ities I might I might like to say
直到城市我可能想说
this mechanism is gonna get run many
这种机制会运行很多
times I don't really care what happens
我真的不在乎会发生什么
one time after another but I care about
一次又一次，但我在乎
my kind of long-run profit or loss so I
我的长期损益，所以我
want to say that on expectation over the
想说的是对
agents valuation
代理商评估
it's the case that I'm strictly budget
确实是我严格的预算
balanced or if I prefer weekly budget
平衡或如果我更喜欢每周预算
balanced here's yet another constraint
平衡这里还有另一个约束
that we often care about
我们经常在乎的
it's called individual rationality and
这被称为个人理性，
the idea of individual rationality is
个人理性的思想是
that I want to encode the idea that
我想对这个想法进行编码
agents might have a choice about whether
代理商可能会选择是否
to participate in the mechanism and so I
参与机制，所以我
want to make it so formally they don't
想要正式地做到这一点，他们不想
have a choice right formally they just
正式有选择权，他们只是
have to choose some action in the
必须选择一些动作
mechanism and it's kind of too bad for
机制，对于
them and payments get imposed on them
他们和付款强加给他们
and they just have to pay whatever it
他们只需要付出任何代价
gets imposed but in practice we might
被强加但实际上我们可能
want to have a condition on the
希望有一个条件
mechanism that says agents actually
实际说代理的机制
would have liked to choose to be part of
本来希望选择成为一部分
this mechanism and in particular we want
这种机制，特别是我们想要的
to say your expected utility for
说出您预期的效用
participating in the mechanism is no
参与机制不是
worse than your expected utility from
比您预期的效用差
staying at home in other words your
换句话说，待在家里
expected utility is weakly positive so
预期效用为弱正数，因此
for example I might care about this X
例如我可能会在意这个X
interim recall that X interim means that
临时回忆X临时意味着
I know what my value is but I don't know
我知道我的价值是什么，但我不知道
the values of anybody else so taking
其他人的价值观
that whole idea that I would be happy to
我很乐意的整个想法
participate in this mechanism knowing my
知道我的参与机制
own value but not knowing everyone
自己的价值，但不认识所有人
else's value here's how I would
其他的价值就是我的意愿
formalize it I say for all agents and
我对所有代理商都说正式化
for all valuations of that agent might
该代理商的所有估值可能
have I'm going to look at the
我要去看看
expectation over everybody else's
对其他人的期望
valuations given my valuation in other
鉴于我的其他估值
words I know the distribution over
我知道的话分布
valuations and so once I observe my
估值，所以一旦我观察到我的
value I can update my beliefs over
可以更新我的信念
everyone else's values taking my own
每个人的价值观都属于我自己
value into account for example our
价值，例如我们的
values might be correlated and so I
值可能是相关的，所以我
might believe different things about
可能会相信不同的事情
your value once I know my value so
你的价值，一旦我知道我的价值
knowing all of that I want to say that a
知道所有这些，我想说
jedi's value for the choice that
绝地的选择价值
actually gets made in equilibrium given
实际上在给定的平衡
both his own equilibrium strategy and
他自己的均衡策略和
the equilibrium strategies of everybody
每个人的均衡策略
else his value for the choice - the
否则他的选择价值-
payment that he makes is greater than or
他支付的款项大于或
equal to zero and again notice that this
等于零，然后再次注意到
is all in equilibrium I'm not saying
都处于平衡状态我不是在说
there's no way to lose in this man
这个男人没有办法输
maybe if everyone else does some
也许如果其他人都做一些
terrible thing then I could actually end
可怕的事情然后我实际上可以结束
up losing on average but if everyone
平均上升，但如果每个人
follows the equilibrium strategy then no
遵循均衡策略，然后否
matter what my type is on average across
不管我的平均水平是多少
everybody else's types I come out ahead
每个人的类型我都领先
or I at least break even that's what X
或我至少要达到X的收支平衡
interim individual rationality says of
临时个人理性说
course I might want something stronger
当然我可能想要更强的东西
so ex post individual rationality says I
所以事后个人理性说我
don't want to average over everybody
不想对所有人平均
else's types maybe I don't want to
其他类型，也许我不想
average because I don't believe that I
一般，因为我不相信我
actually know this distribution of
实际上知道
everybody else's types or maybe I just
其他人的类型，也许我只是
want a stronger condition that says I
想要一个更坚强的条件，说我
don't ever want to be in a situation
永远都不想遇到这种情况
where in equilibrium I would lose so
在平衡中我会因此失去
here I get rid of this expectation over
在这里，我摆脱了这种期望
types and I change this quantification
类型，我更改此量化
over my value into a quantification over
将我的价值量化为
everybody's values all at once so what I
每个人的价值观都是一次
say is for all agents and for all joint
对所有代理人和所有联合人员说
values that they all might have it's
他们都可能拥有的价值观
always the case sort of point wise in
总是在某种程度上明智
this set of values that my value for the
这套价值是我对
choice that gets made - my payment is
做出的选择-我的付款是
always greater than or equal to zero so
总是大于或等于零，所以
this is a stronger condition if I'm
如果我
ex-post individual rational I'm always
事后个人理性我永远
going to be accepted of individual
会被个人接受
rational but the reverse is not
理性的，但反过来不是
necessarily true here's one last
一定是真的，这是最后一个
condition to talk about tractability so
关于易处理性的条件
far we've talked about economic
到目前为止，我们已经谈到经济
conditions that talk about the nature of
关于...的性质的条件
the choice that gets made by the
由...做出的选择
mechanism or the nature of the payments
付款机制或性质
that get imposed well here I want to say
我想说的很好
that these actual functions the acts
这些实际功能的行为
function that chooses the choice and the
选择选项和功能的功能
P function that chooses the payments are
选择付款的P函数是
each computable in polynomial time and
每个可在多项式时间内计算
turns out that some of the mechanisms
原来有些机制
that we're going to turn out to be
我们将证明是
interested in don't have this property
感兴趣的没有此属性
so it's sometimes the case that the
所以有时候
computational problem of figuring out
计算出的计算问题
what choice to make and how much to
做出什么选择以及要做什么
charge everybody can be a hard
收费每个人都很难
computational problem and what this
计算问题以及这是什么
means is we might be worried that for
意味着我们可能会担心
large inputs we just couldn't run the
大量的投入我们根本无法运行
mechanism we wouldn't have enough time
机制，我们将没有足够的时间
on any reasonable computational device
在任何合理的计算设备上
to find out the answer and if that's
找出答案，如果那是
true then there's something wrong with
是的，那有什么问题
the mechanism because we might worry
该机制，因为我们可能会担心
that we just couldn't run it so we might
我们只是无法运行它，所以我们可能
like to make a restriction that says I
喜欢说我的限制
want a guarantee that I can actually
想要我可以保证
evaluate these functions tractable and a
评估这些功能易于处理并
common definition of tractability in
易处理性的通用定义
computer science is the guarantee that
计算机科学是保证
something can be done in polynomial time
可以在多项式时间内完成
okay so much for constraints that we
很好的约束，我们
want to impose now let's think about
现在要强加让我们考虑一下
objective functions that we might place
我们可能放置的目标功能
on our mechanism here's one I might
在我们的机制上，我可能会
actually like revenue so maybe I'm
其实喜欢收入，所以也许我
selling something and I want a mechanism
卖东西，我想要一种机制
that does the best that it can it
尽其所能
satisfies various constraints maybe it's
满足各种约束，也许是
going to ensure individual rationality
要确保个人理性
so people will want to participate maybe
所以人们可能想参加
it's gonna be a weekly budget balance so
这将是每周预算余额，因此
that I know I never lose money but then
我知道我永远不会亏钱，但是
maybe it's gonna be truthful but then
也许会是真实的，但是
once these constraints are satisfied
一旦满足这些约束
they're still going to be maybe a space
他们仍然可能是一个空间
of different mechanisms that would
不同的机制
satisfy those constraints and within
满足这些约束并且在
that space I might want to say that I
这个空间我可能想说
want to pick the mechanism that gives me
想选择给我的机制
as much revenue as possible
尽可能多的收入
so I'll call that mechanism revenue
所以我称该机制为收益
maximizing and a mechanism is revenue
最大化，机制就是收益
maximizing when among all functions X
在所有功能中最大化X
and P that satisfy whatever other
和P满足其他条件
constraints it is that we care about the
约束是我们关心
mechanism selects those that maximizes
机制选择那些最大化
the expectation over the agents types of
对代理商类型的期望
the sum of the payments where this
付款总额
denotes the agents equilibrium strategy
表示代理商均衡策略
profile notice here I'm using the the
我在这里使用的个人资料通知
theta notation for types instead of
类型的theta符号代替
values but but the the sense of it is
价值观，但其意义在于
the same so the next of objective
一样，所以下一个目标
function that we might care about is
我们可能关心的功能是
actually to minimize the amount of
实际上最小化
revenue that the mechanism collects and
机制收取的收入和
this makes sense if I don't actually
如果我实际上不这样做，这是有道理的
want the mechanism to make money but I
想要赚钱的机制，但我
just wanted to make a good decision and
只是想做出一个好的决定而
the only reason that I have payments at
我付款的唯一原因
all is that quasi-linear or mechanism
都是准线性或机制
design is easier than mechanism design
设计比机构设计容易
when I don't have payments based on
当我没有付款依据时
impossibility theorems that you've
你已经不可能定理
already seen so and I might just prefer
已经看过了，我可能更喜欢
strict budget balance that might be the
严格的预算余额可能是
best thing but there are cases where
最好的事情，但在某些情况下
strict budget balance is impossible to
严格的预算平衡是不可能的
so I might just want to minimize the
所以我可能只想最小化
amount of revenue that I collect so what
我收取的收入金额是多少
I might do is make it constraint for
我可能会做的是限制它
week budget balance say at least I never
周预算余额说，至少我从来没有
want to lose money and then I want to
想亏钱，然后我想
collect as little as possible so I can
收集尽可能少的，所以我可以
formalize this here by saying saying
通过说说来在这里正式化
what follows let me just note what you
接下来的事情让我只注意你
see here at the bottom before I go
在我走之前，先在底部看到
through the definition I'm just for fun
通过定义我只是为了好玩
I'm gonna do this as a worst case over
我要在最坏的情况下这样做
evaluations rather than an expectation
评价而不是期望
like I did in the previous slide so I'll
就像我在上一张幻灯片中所做的那样，
say that a transferable utility
说一个可转让的实用程序
mechanism is revenue minimizing when
机制是收益最小化
again considering all of the functions X
再次考虑所有功能X
and P that satisfy whatever other
和P满足其他条件
constraints we have the mechanism
约束，我们有机制
selects those that minimize the maximum
选择那些使最大值最小的那些
over the agents valuations of the sum of
超过代理商总和的估值
the payments in their equilibrium
付款处于均衡状态
strategy profile so here what I'm saying
策略简介，这就是我要说的
is that in the worst case worst from the
是最坏的情况是
point of view of the minimization
最小化的观点
problem so in the case where the
问题是在
valuations cause me to collect the most
估价使我收集最多
revenue I want to make that number as
我想将这个数字设为
little as possible and of course I can
尽可能少，我当然可以
do this with an average as well okay
平均也可以做到这一点
another thing I might care about is
我可能关心的另一件事是
fairness I might want to say my
公平我可能想说我的
mechanism is as fair as possible now
现在的机制是尽可能公平的
this might be something I want to say
这也许是我想说的
but it turns out it's pretty hard to
但事实证明，很难
formalize so let me give you an example
形式化，让我给你一个例子
consider these two cases and ask
考虑这两种情况并询问
yourself which of them do you think it's
自己，您认为其中的哪个
fair is fair so first of all I might ask
公平是公平的，所以首先我可能会问
what about a case where I charge all of
如果我收取全部费用
the agents a hundred dollars and I make
代理商一百美元，我赚
a choice that everybody hates secondly
每个人都讨厌的选择
consider a case where I charge all
考虑一下我全部负责的情况
agents zero dollars and I make a choice
代理商零美元，我做出选择
that some of them hate and some of them
他们当中有些人讨厌而另一些人
like well there's a sense in which the
就像在某种意义上
first one is really fair because it's
第一个很公平，因为
the same for everybody but we still sort
每个人都一样，但我们仍然在排序
of have the sense that the second one is
的感觉，第二个是
better we wouldn't want a sense of
更好的是，我们不想
fairness that just talks about equality
谈论平等的公平
because doing something terrible to
因为做一些可怕的事情
everybody doesn't seem like a good way
每个人似乎都不是一个好方法
to design a mechanism so so I'd like
设计一种机制，所以我想
some kind of definition of fairness then
那么对公平的某种定义
nevertheless says that the second thing
尽管如此，第二件事
is better than the first thing and their
比第一件事和他们的要好
variety of different definitions but
各种不同的定义，但是
here's one that I like
这是我喜欢的一个
max-min fairness so this says I want to
最大最小公平，所以这说我想
look over all the agents and how they do
查看所有代理商及其行为
in the mechanism figure out who is the
在机制中找出谁是
least happy and then make that person
最不开心，然后让那个人
the happiest so I want to look at the
最幸福的，所以我想看看
person in society who gets sort of the
社会上的人
worst deal in this mechanism and then
这种机制最糟糕的交易，然后
how things become as good as possible
事情如何变得尽可能好
for that person so I might recognize
为那个人，所以我可能会意识到
that there's going to be some inequality
将会有一些不平等
in my mechanism but I'm going to focus
在我的机制中，但我要集中精力
on the worst outcome and make it as good
在最坏的结果上，并使其表现出色
as I can so I'll say formally then a
尽我所能，我会正式说
mechanism is maximum fare when among the
在以下情况下，该机制是最高票价：
functions X and P that satisfy whatever
满足任何条件的函数X和P
other constraints that I have the
我有的其他限制
mechanism selects those that maximizes
机制选择那些最大化
the expectation over the agents values
对代理商价值的期望
of the minimum over the agents of their
超过其代理商的最低数量
expected utility so I want to maximize
预期的效用，所以我想最大化
the expected value of the worst case
最坏情况的期望值
here's the last thing I want to talk
这是我想谈的最后一件事
about price of Anarchy minimization so
关于无政府状态最小化的价格
before when I talked about revenue
在我谈到收入之前
minimization I was kind of relaxing
最小化我有点放松
strict budget balance in a case where I
如果我有严格的预算平衡
couldn't really have strict budget
真的没有严格的预算
balance I said well let me take
平衡我说得好让我接受
basically let me take this idea of
基本上让我接受这个想法
collecting little revenue and put it
收取很少的收入并投入
into the objective function I can do the
进入目标函数，我可以做到
same thing with efficiency so it might
有效率的同一件事，所以可能
be that strict efficiency is impossible
严格的效率是不可能的
or is too costly in terms of other
或在其他方面过于昂贵
things that I care about in the
我在乎的事情
mechanism and so I might put that into
机制，所以我可能会将其纳入
the objective function and say I want a
目标函数，说我想要一个
mechanism that is as close to efficient
接近效率的机制
as possible so in particular I may want
尽可能的特别是我可能想要
to minimize the worst case ratio between
使之间的最坏情况比率最小化
the optimal social welfare that could be
可能的最佳社会福利
achieved and the social welfare that the
实现的社会福利
mechanism actually does achieve and this
机制实际上确实实现了这一点
ratio is called the price of Anarchy
比率称为无政府状态的价格
it's the difference between the very
这是非常
best thing that could happen and the
可能发生的最好的事情
thing that actually happens when agents
代理商实际发生的事情
act strategically in equilibrium so
在均衡状态下采取战略行动
formally a transferable utility
正式可转让的实用程序
mechanism minimizes the price of Anarchy
机制将无政府状态的价格降至最低
when among all the functions X and P
在所有功能X和P中
that satisfy the other constraints it
满足其他约束
selects those that minimize this ratio
选择那些最小化此比率的
so the ratio is the maximum over all of
因此比率是所有
the choices that could be made of the
可以做出的选择
sum of the agents utilities divided by
代理商效用之和除以
so this is the social welfare this is
所以这是社会福利
the best social welfare that I could
我能做到的最好的社会福利
have and I'm going to divide that by the
有，我将除以
sum over all the agents of the values
将所有值的主体相加
that they actually obtain in equilibrium
他们实际上在平衡中获得的
for the choice that actually gets made
对于实际做出的选择
and I'm going to look in the worst case
我要看最坏的情况
here over all values I'm going to look
在这里，我要看的所有价值观
at the the set of values that makes this
在使这
as bad as it can be and then I'm going
尽其所能然后我要去
to try to minimize this by choosing X
尝试通过选择X将其最小化
and P that make this worst case price of
和P使得这个最坏情况的价格
Anarchy as little as it can be so those
无政府状态越少越好
are all of the constraints and objective
是所有的约束和目标
functions that I'm going to define for
我将要定义的功能
you today overall you can kind of
您今天总体上可以
imagine just listing them all and
想象一下，只列出它们，
essentially having an optimization
本质上有优化
problem that says I want to find the X
我想找到X的问题
and the P that maximize or minimize
和最大化或最小化的P
whatever objective function I care about
我关心的任何目标函数
subject to various constraints on how X
受到X的各种限制
and P work in terms of things like
和P在诸如
budget individual rationality
预算个人理性
truthfulness and so on
真实性等